

T'Keyah Marshall

UX Designer

Snapshot

Fashion and Beauty professional with 10+ years of visual design and merchandising, management and operational experience. Seeking career pivot within design industry to collaborate creatively while utilizing prior business training.

Skillset

HTML • CSS • JS • Github •
Adobe Suite • Figma • Graphic
Design • Procreate • Editing •
Customer Experience • Visual
Merchandising • Product
Knowledge • Team Onboarding

Contact

portfolio tknyma.com email tknyma94@gmail.com cell (215) 602 9895



Experience

Footwear Buyer

2017 - present | SnipesUSA

Created digital training materials for merchandising and inventory reporting applications. Contributed last minute store communication graphics in response to product release changes. Researched databases and merchant portals to review past and future orders for accuracy.

Visual Merchandise Manager

2016 - 2017 | L'Oreal #MAKEUP

Designed marketing materials for social media, email advertising and floorset visuals. Digital creation of KPI tools. Effectively planned and executed visual directives.

Assistant Store Manager

2012 - 2015 | ICING by Claire's

Created location specific flyer mockups for partnered marketing events. Developed digital lookbooks for consumer personas.

Education

Google UX Design Professional Certificate 2021 | Coursera

B.A. Liberal Arts 2016 - 2018 | Rowan University

Transfer Credit 2012 - 2015 | Atlantic Cape CC

H.S. Diploma 2008 - 2012 | Winslow Twp HS

References

Shannon Payton - Senior Buyer (908) 230 4665

Melanie Robins - Brand Coordinator (410) 530 8325

Alexus Robinson - Store Manager (215) 500 9647